Guide to the Hapgood Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize, 1854-1940; 1.75; (1 box)
  - WRITINGS
    - Hutchins Hapgood
      - Books
        - David, the Story of a Soul: printed version in The Musical Advance, pp. 3-7 [installment], 1913 May (Box 48, Folder 1531)
        - "Letters from a Ballet Girl": draft fragments, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1532)
        - The Story of a Lover: book reviews, 1919 Sep 28 (Box 48, Folder 1533)
        - A Victorian in the Modern World
          - Research notes, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1534)
          - Draft fragments, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1535)
          - Advertisements, ca. 1939 (Box 48, Folder 1536)
      - Shorter Works
        Articles
        - "The Criminal Monkey": printed version in The Socialist War, 1917 Apr (Box 48, Folder 1537)
    - Neith Boyce Hapgood
      - Shorter Works
        Book Reviews
        - "Chesterton," in Harper's Weekly, review of Chesterton, G. K., Magic and The Flying Inn: galley proof (Box 48, Folder 1538)
  - FAMILY PAPERS
    - Maps
      - Map of Key West, Florida, 1935 Feb (Box 48, Folder 1539)
      - Map of shorefront property, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1540)
    - Photographs
      - Hapgood, Harry Boyce, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1541)
      - Hapgood, Hutchins, n.d.
      - Hapgood, Hutchins and Miriam (Box 48, Folder 1542)
      - Hapgood, Hutchins and Neith Boyce
        - [scene from the play Enemies in (Provincetown, Massachusetts)], 1916
      - Hapgood, Neith Boyce, n.d.
      - O'Brien, Joe, n.d.
    - Subject Files
      - Drawings by various family members, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1543)
      - Hapgood, Emma Frances, 1854 Jul 4 (Box 48, Folder 1544)
      - Hapgood, Hutchins: Harvard University, Diploma from [B.A.], 1892 Jun 29 (Box 48, Folder 1545)
      - Luhan, Mabel Dodge: general, 1914-40, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1546)
    - Miscellaneous Papers
      - Miscellaneous Papers, ca. 1880 (Box 48, Folder 1547)